<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="90264" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="SmartTransportation" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="This mod automates ticket prices and number of vehicles in transit routes" />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<!--LongDescription Value="This is a long description" /-->
	<LongDescription>
This mod automates ticket prices and number of vehicles in transit routes. This will make your transit system smarter and able to adapt to peak and off-peak hours.

## Transit Section

It is possible to configure how the mod will adjust transit routes for each mode (Bus, Tram, Subway and Train). The settings that can be changed include:

* **Ticket Price:** The user can configure the maximum fare increase and decrease for each transit mode. Fares will increase when vehicles are full to increase revenue and discourage more ridership, and they will decrease when vehicles are empty to encourage more riders.
* **Target Occupancy:** The mod will change number of vehicles and adjust fares to try to reach the target occupancy. However, because there is a limit on the number of vehicles per route and also on the fare increase and decrease, the target occupancy might not be met in some cases. Also, a high target occupancy might decrease the frequency of transit vehicles, which consequently might discourage transit ridership. So choose wisely.
* **Disable:** It is also possible to disable adjustments for each mode. In this case, the vehicle count and ticket price will remain with the previous values.

## Settings Section

The settings tab has some settings that affects all transit modes. These include:

* **Waiting Time Weight:** When calculating occupancy, the mod trys to predict ridership by considering the number of weighting passengers at transit stops. Assuming that once those passengers board, a number of passengers that are in the vehicle will deboard, this weight will be applied to the number of waiting passengers to reduce their effect in the occupancy calculation.
* **Target Occupancy Threshold:** When the mod compares a route occupancy with the target occupancy, it will consider the threshold within the target when making a decision. Default value is 10% but can be changed if desired.
* **Write Transit Information to Log:** This option will write information such as occupancy and number of vehicles for each route to the log every time the mod evaluates a route. This is useful for debugging and understanding why the mod is picking certain ticket price or number of vehicles for each route.

	</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshot.png" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/smart-transportation-mod.1704128/" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="0.2.1" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.1.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
	<Dependency Id="" />
	<ChangeLog>
* Fixed bug that didn't set ticket price to zero
* Added reset button
	</ChangeLog>
	<!--External link. supported types are discord, github, youtube, twitch, x, paypal, patreon-->
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/ruzbeh0/SmartTransportation" />
	<ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.com/channels/1024242828114673724/1285954236647211130" />
	<ExternalLink Type="paypal" Url="https://www.paypal.com/paypalme/ruzbeh0" />
	<ExternalLink Type="kofi" Url="https://ko-fi.com/ruzbeh0" />
</Publish>
